Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 17= (Don't You Remember Me?)
=الحلقة 17= (ألا تتذكرني؟)
Chi Yu, what's the matter with you?
تشي يو، ما الأمر معك؟
Chi Yu, what really happened?
تشي يو، ماذا حدث حقًا؟
Chi Yu, what are you doing?
تشي يو ماذا تفعل؟
No...
لا...
Chi Yu...
تشي يو...
Chi Yu, it's me. Chi Yu...
تشي يو، هذا أنا. تشي يو...
Chi Yu!
تشي يو!
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
You still remember me, right?
هل مازلت تتذكرني، أليس كذلك؟
(Don't worry, Chi Yu.)
(لا تقلق، تشي يو.)
(I'll reclaim the golden phoenix feather for you.)
(سوف أستعيد لك ريشة الفينيق الذهبية.)
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
What a good boy.
يا له من ولد جيد.
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
It's raw. You can't eat it.
إنه نيء، لا يمكنك أكله.
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
This is inedible too.
وهذا غير صالح للأكل أيضًا.
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
You may have this.
ربما لديك هذا.
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
(Chi Yu.)
(تشي يو.)
(You will get well eventually.)
(سوف تتحسن حالتك في نهاية المطاف.)
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
You.
أنت.
Chi
ينفق
Yu.
يو.
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
Me?
أنا؟
Mu
في
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
Ling...
آخر...
xue.
شيويه.
Mu Lingxue.
مو لينج شيو.
(Chi)
(ينفق)
(Yu.)
(يو.)
My name
اسمي
is Chi Yu.
هو تشي يو.
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
Chi Yu. Chi Yu.
تشي يو. تشي يو.
(Mu Lingxue.)
(مو لينج شيو.)
(Chi Yu.)
(تشي يو.)
Mu Lingxue.
مو لينج شيو.
That's me.
هذا انا.
That's my name.
هذا اسمي.
You remember it, don't you?
هل تتذكر ذلك؟
Chi Yu, what's it?
تشي يو، ما الأمر؟
Let's go now.
دعنا نذهب الآن.
We're leaving this place.
نحن نغادر هذا المكان.
I'm alright.
انا بخير.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
This is how you
هذه هي الطريقة التي
comfort someone.
مواساة شخص ما.
Do it gently.
افعل ذلك بلطف.
Have you found her?
هل وجدتها؟
According to the scout's report,
وفقا لتقرير الكشاف،
Her Highness was spotted in the woods in the outskirts of the city.
تم رصد سموها في الغابة على مشارف المدينة.
Looks like
يبدو مثل
she was forcibly taken away by that bodyguard.
لقد تم أخذها بالقوة من قبل ذلك الحارس الشخصي.
Her accurate whereabouts remain unknown.
ولا يزال مكان تواجدها غير معروف على وجه الدقة.
He sure was bold.
لقد كان جريئا بالتأكيد.
Issue this decree of mine.
أصدر هذا المرسوم مني.
Rescue her
انقذها
no matter what it costs.
بغض النظر عن التكلفة.
As for that bodyguard,
أما بالنسبة لذلك الحارس الشخصي،
I'm going
انا ذاهب
to give him an ugly death.
لإعطائه موتًا قبيحًا.
Chi Yu, what's wrong with you?
تشي يو، ما الخطأ معك؟
Chi Yu, wake up!
تشي يو، استيقظ!
What's happened?
ماذا حدث؟
He's had my Phantom Fox's Mind Bewitching Technique.
لقد كان لديه تقنية سحر العقل الخاصة بـ Phantom Fox.
So he's not going to wake up.
لذلك فهو لن يستيقظ.
Kill her.
اقتليها
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
Chi Yu!
تشي يو!
(He's actually managed)
(لقد تمكن فعلا)
(to get rid of the Phantom Fox's Mind Bewitching Technique.)
(للتخلص من تقنية سحر العقل الخاصة بـ Phantom Fox.)
Chi Yu!
تشي يو!
Her Highness is over there!
صاحبة السمو هناك!
Quick!
سريع!
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 17=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 17=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪